Hello Everyone
I'm Mikami Yua From S1
This Work Is
A 6 Years Work As A Documentary
Porn Movie Photography
After 6 Years, What I Am The Growing Up
There Are Also Many Changes
Everyone, Please Do Watch This Work
Watch My 6 Years Documentary
Let's Get To The Topic
-Hello
-Congratulations To The 6th Anniversary For Your Porn Movie Career
-Thanks But Not Yet
Not Yet?Sorry
Then Next Is The Intimate Photography
Okay
Please
There Is One More Today, Right?
-Yes
-Two Personal Photography
You Are Very Tall
No, Not At All
By The Way, That
I Rarely Took A Interview, So
I Want To Hear
It's Okay, Can You Smell It?
Yes
So The First Question Is
-It's Has Not Been Six Years Yet, Right?
-Yes
Feel The Time Pass Fast Or Slow
It Is Hard To Say
Both
I Can't Feel That
Do You Feel That Sometimes That The Time Pass Fast?
A Moment
In Retrospect
There Are Still Many
So Objectively
-Okay
-These 6 Years
A Lot Of Things Happened To Me
Yes
What's Wrong
-Can I Ask
Yes, Okay
Then Next
I Want To Ask A Question
Do You Remember The First And The Second Year?
Do You?
I Was Very Busy A Few Years Ago
Before 3 Years
I Was So Busy
I Don't Remember How Long I Did What
These Have Been Recorded
-That's Great. Did You Record It?
-Yes
Oh Yeah
And
How Many Works Have You Shot
Not Quite Clearly, A Lot
Yes
First Of All, You Are Very Fashionable
-Okay
-I'm Going To Start Photography
The Weather Is So Good. It Is Sunny, Right?
-Indeed
-Yes
-I Actually Don't Like The Sun
I Hate The Sun
Although I Like Summer Very Much
But The Curtains Will Be Drawn At Home
No Sunny
-Really?
-Yes, No Sunshine Usually
I Hate The Sun
But The Sun Likes Me Very Much
Like This
-Didn't I Take A Car?-Yes
There Is Sunshine Everywhere
Absolutely Yes
I Also Changed Seats Several Times Yesterday
3 Times, And All Came Here Again
Completely Shine Me
Really
The Sun Really Likes Me
Although I Don't Like It In August
-Pretty Good
-Yes
-I Feel That I Am Being Loved
-Yes, By The Sun.
Yes, But Cloudy Is Better
Although I Am Very Happy, But Very Few
I Don't Like The Sun Very Much
You Will Be Noticed By The Chairman
Yes, We Are Forbidden To Fall In Love On Work
What About The Rest
No Problem
Only Me, That. .
I Can Get Tanned Easily
-You Won't Be Angry Today, Right?
-I Will Try My Best
But If You Go, You Will Get A Tan
But Do You Hate Tanning.
-Although I Hate It
I Like Warm Places
If I Am An Ordinary Person
I Want To Go To The Beach Without Caring
Won't You Go Before?
When I Was 18 Or 19 Years Old
I Left SKE As An Improper Idol
I've Been There, I Was Very Happy
So Do You Hardly Go Now?
-My Dad Works On The Beach
-Is That So?
Yes, I Used To Go To The Beach When I Was Very Young
I Am Already A Tanned Girl
When I Was A Kid As The Tanned Girl
Here We Are
Here Is Awesome It's Pretty Good
I Don't Know If My Dad Is Here Or Not
(Mikami Yua's 6th Anniversary Debut)
Watch JAV English Subtitles
JAVENGLISH.CC | ~ JAVENGLISH.NET ~ | JAVSUBBED.NET
(S1)
(Ultimate Sex)
(Real 5 Times)
-Good Morning
Great, This Is The First One
The Wind Is So Strong
The Wind Blows In The Mouth
-Is It Suddenly?
-It Is Very Slight
-Are You Okay
-Yes
Sorry
-Let's Talk Seriously
-Okay
How About This Time
Can You Say
-So
-Okay
There Will Be An Interview
We Will Ask You Some Questions, We Will Try Our Best Not To Cause Troubles
Okay
You Used To Be An Idol (Looking Back On The Past)
From 2009 To 2014?
-2014
Until 2014-14
-Until 2014
-Until?
-Yes
-That Was So Long
Not Really
-I Have Searched On The Internet
-OK
How Many
Indeed
Why Did You Be An Idol?
The Motive Is?
I Liked Idols Since I Was A Kid
I Have Been Supported
Later, I Wanted To Become An Idol
I Didn't Expect That
I Searched And Participated In The Election By Myself
Didn't The Family Take The Initiative?
-Not At All
-Did You Think About It?
Have You Been There Several Times?
Have You Been To SKE?
Were There Any Workmates?
Yes, My Contemporaries
That Knew I Was Shooting Porn Movie At That Time
Someone Should Know, Although They Rarely Talk About It
Then I Quit By Myself
Why Did You Quit?
It Was In The Second Grade Of Middle School
My Parents Never Thought I Would Be An Idol
When I Applied
I Said I Was Qualified
They Told Me It Was Troublesome To Go To Work
From Nagoya To Tokyo
My Mom Was Also Working
I Had To Go With Mom
Then I Was Rejected
I Was Actually Supported For The First Time
Was In The Morning Musume Group
Then I Passed Through SKE
After That, I Thought
There Should Be A Chance
Then I Quit By Myself
I Went To SKE
Yes, But I Failed For The First Round Of Selection
But Went Through For The Second
Were The Competitors Too Good?
No, It Was My Own Problem
Some Problems
When The Final Review
Selection Of SKE
But Finally Lost
I Wondered If My Foundation Was Not Good
And I Thought I Couldn't Take That Job
So I Reflected
After Selection
Although I Don't Know Why
I Would Never Say At That Time
It Will Be A Bit Negative
Young Girl Is Oh Yeah
They Study Hard
I Just Said That We Were The Same Age
-How Is That?
-Not At All
The Previous Life
Let's Talk About Your Idol Career
Okay
Did You Work Hard?
Yes, In The Life Of An Idol
Actually, I Also Had Some Ideas
That Is
Maybe Compared To Ordinary Idols
1 Am A Bad Idol
Because I Lost My Job
I Feel That I Had Caused Troubles To Everyone
About Fans
I Also Made Them Sad
But
A Lot Of Things Happened To Me
How To Say
I'm Very Happy To Work Hard With The Members
When I Looked Back, I Also Feel
That Was Also A Very Important Time
Didn't You Feel Do You Feel Uncomfortable?
No, I Was Very Happy
Because I Had Been Becoming An Idol
So Every Day
The First Handshake And Concert
I Was Doing What I Was Looking Forward To
When I Received My Own Clothes
Everytime
I Was Happy
Although It Was Difficult But Also Very Happy
I See
Were You Really Happy?
Yes, I Could Not Stop At That Time.
How Did You Feel?
Uhh
-Sorry
-Anything Is Okay
-About Love
-Yes
Have You Ever Been In Love
When I Was An Idol
Did You Have A Boyfriend
No
-Really?
-Yes
Really?
Yes
Uhh, Not Completely No
But There Was True Love
Is That So?
Yes, Unrequited Love Is Not Bad
-Really?
-Although I Can't Have A Two-Way Relationship
But If You Are In Love
For Girls Who Care About That
It's Also An Opportunity To Be Cute
The Reason Why This Can Be Unrequited Love
So Unrequited Love For 5 Years?
Not At All
Yes
How To Say
I Can't Remember
But I Have Changed
Change?
It's Not Good If I Was Exposed
I Will Be Discovered
I Can't Say Anything
Have You Ever Been Forbidden In Love?
But I Broke The Rules
It's Good
-Yes
-Have You Had A Lot Of Bf Before?
-No
-Isn't It?
-Yes
-I Feel There Were A Lot
So Why Did You Start Porn Movie?
Everyone Thought I Had A Scandal, But No
I Did Not Expect
I Didn't Expect There Would Be
Not Because The Scandal
Maybe Something Like That Happened
But I Was 20 Years Old
I Did Not Have Much Responsibility For Work
Than Now
In A Nice Group
I Made Myself Swell
As One Of Them
I Didn't Have To Do Anything
I Just Need To Hold Hands And Perform
CD Can Also Be Sold. So In Common Sense
I Didn't Think Of Myself As A Member Too Much
You Are Very Serious
Yes
I Hope I Could Be Serious Before
Then I Know The Cause Of The Scandal
-It's Also A Reason To Leave
-Okay
Isn't There A Blank Period?
-Yes
-During That Time
What Did You Do
I Have Decided To Do This Job
Have You Talked About It?
Yes, When I Graduated
-Really?
-Yes
It's Not A Contract Anymore
But For The Next
I Can Make A Good Decision And Then Resign
I Don't Want To Lost Everything When I Resign
When I Was 20 Years Old
I Had Decided It Too
Think About The Past
Decided And Then Resigned
I Had Already Decided At That Time
Did You Feel Lost?
Yes, But I Didn't Tell Anyone
I Was Afraid I Would Be Persuaded If I Told
For Example, It's Better To Resign
I Don't Want To Hear This Opinion
I Want To Decide By Myself
Although I Was Loss
But It Would Changed Without Taking This Step
And I Don't Wanna Have A Boring Life
So I Was Not Too Confused
I Don't Remember At That Time
But I Was Not Keeping Staying No Home
Then You Have A Lot Of Friends, Right?
Yes, A Lot Of People Think So
I Have Decided
But There Is No Such Kind Of Friends Around
Everyone
Is All The Same
I Had No Experience At That Time
-When You Were As An Idol?
-Yes
I Didn't Want To Be An Idol
But There Were Many People Who Supported Me
About The Next Career
Debut With A Change Of Name
Great Changes In Mood
-I Feel That I Have Learned A Lot
-No
-Really?
-I Resigned Because I Thought I Didn't Have
-I Think What I Should Do Is Over
Absolutely Not
Now The Idol Is Hard
Really?
-Is That The Decision?
-Yes
I Like To See Myself
When I Did That
I Feel There Is Nothing I Can Do As An Idol
Oh Yeah
Don't You Resist?
I Want To Start Something New
Porn Movie Actress May Have Some Problems
But I Want To Change Myself
I Feel That There Is No Other Way
There Is Nothing Else I Can Do
So I Can Only Work Hard Here
-Then Let's Talk About Other Things
-OK
-Your First Work Is In May?
-Yes
-Being Sold In June. But May Is Information.
-Yes.
-Indeed
-Yes
You Said You Were Discovered By Your Mother
I Told Her Before May 1st
A Few Days Ago
How Did You Say
I Said I Started Photography 3 Months Ago
Why Did You Say So
I Was Ready To Say I Was Going To Take Photography
In Short, She Needed Some Time To Accept
She Told Me Not To Contact Her
I Didn't Plan To Do This
I Don't Want To Make Concessions In Life
3 Months Later, My Mom Sent Me A Message
I Don't Remember How Long, But It's Very Short.
She Completely Accepted That After 3 Months
Yes, I Don't Fully Accept It Now
About My Porn Movie Actress Career
She Did Not Accept
And She Didn't Support Me
But After Watching My Activities In Recent Years
She Didn't Say But Agreed
But She Can't Support My Work
I See
Alright
-Thank You For Telling Me
-Okay
As An Actress
-Your Have Changed
-Yes
Is There Anything Special
Special
The Way Fans Treat Me
Nothing Else
The New Fan Or The Previous Ones?
Not Many Previous Fans
Maybe More Now
For Those Who Support Me Now
And Before
I Treat Everyone In The Same Way
This Is A Serious Topic
The Same As Porn Movie
Then Do You Remember Your First Work?
Almost
-The Actor Is Coming
-Yes
Take It Off, I See The Cock
How Do You Feel?
I Can't Remember Who Was The First Actor
I Feel So Weird
I Didn't Think I Was Not An Idol At That Time
I Can't Believe That Someone Show His Cock
In Front Of Me?
What The Hell Was This
I Completely Do Not Understand
This
Was Embarrassed
Really?
I Have Said It Now
When The First Work
I Felt Explosive At That Time
-I Can't Say It Now
-Really?
When Filming The First Work
I Thought About It For A Long Time
About How To Make Good Work
Everyone Worked Hard Too
We Wanna More People See
Wanna Try My Best
Try Hard
I Guess Everyone Is Like This
The First Work Is Very Important
The First One Has Its Own Exclusive Charm
Worked Hard For This
Of Course I Had My Own Ideas
But I Have Worked Hard
It Was The First One That I Thought About A Long Time
Uhh
The First Work Was Watching The Scene Of A Cock Cum
Was There Such A Scene
I Can't Remember
The Second One
-First Time
-Yes
I Can't Remember, When 1 Took Off
Yes
Ken Shimizu Was Here
Did You Know The Porn Movie Actor?
No, I Don't Know.
And About Ken Shimizu, ! Only Met Him After Becoming An Actress
I Didn't Know Him Before
What? That Guy Kept Sucking
Indeed
Armpit Or Something
And Assholes, Sucked It All
Obviously We Just Met, But Why Did He Do That?
It Was Incredible
Didn't You Say Stop It?
No, This Is Photography
I Have To Work Well
-But
-What's Wrong
Not Very Disgusting
How About The Second One?
I Could Be Able To Act But I Didn't Do It
Yes
Compared With That Time
-Now?
-You Have Grown Up
No, Because It Was Fresh
That Feeling Has Gradually Disappeared
So The Mood At That Time
I Want To Remember
But I Am Also Used To This Career
So This Is Daily
I Can Tell Some Adult's Jokes Now
I Want To Remember The Mood Of Being An Idol
But
I Did Grew Up As An Actress
I Don't Know. Let People Judge
Do You Think There Is Any Growth Of You?
A Lot, What Do You Think
-It's Oh Yeah
-But It Was At The Beginning
That Is Good
I Work Hard
Pretty Good
-Can't This Be Useful?
-Yes
But Porn Movie Is Hard To Act
Not Good Or Bad, Besides
There Are Many Good Things
So How Do You Say About Others
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
And So
Who Would You Imitate
I Will Watch Other People's Work
Fair Enough
But I Don't Think There Is A Correct Answer
I Can Only Cheer
Do You Rarely Imitate?
I Don't Watch Porn Movie Works
Yes
I Saw It My First Work
-I Watched A Few.
-How Did You Feel??
I Was Popular At That Time
The Retired Actress Like
Minoru
Angel Moe
People In The Leaderboard
Sakura Mauna
So For This Kind Of High Popularity
I Will Take A Look At Their Works
I Will Take A Look
And I Will Know
So I Don't Know The Current Actress
-I Don't Even Look At My Own
-Is It Self?
Self-Sex
Okay, Thank You
Then It's Over
-Is It Over? Thank You
-There Is One More
-More Interviews?
-Yes
-Really?Thank You
-Thank You
I See
Self-Sex
The Last Self-Sex
Is That OK
-Thanks
-Okay
What A Great Look
Look
Are You So Excited
Yes
Do You Do You Wanna Do It? Nasty Things?
Yes, I Do You Wanna Do It? It Quickly
Horny Pig
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
-Come On
-Okay
Little Pig, Look At Here
Okay
Come On
Open Your Mouth
Go On
-Is It Delicious?
-Yes
Very Delicious
-Do You Wanna More?
-Yes
Yes
-How About This?
-Yes
Go On
-Do You Wanna Go On?
-Yes
Keep Caressing Me
-Come On
-Okay
-Lie Down
Yes
-Feeling Good, Right?
-Yes
My Ears Are Feeling So Good
Fuck Yeah
-Lie Down
-Okay
-Feeling Good, Right?
-Yes
Yes
Come Here
Okay
Suck Me
-Nipples
-How It Feels
This Is So Good
-Feeling Good, Right?
-Yes
-How About Here?
-Don't Move
-Okay
Yes
-Is That So
-Yes
Yes
-Such A Embarrassing Posture
-Yes
-Are You Feeling High?
How About Here
Look
Yes
So Big
This. .
Your Cock Is So Big
I Want To See Your Pussy
Not Yet
Yes, Still Not Yet?
Yes
Here And There
Has It Finished
-What's Wrong
-I Want More
Come On
-Are You Feeling Good With Here?
-Yes
-Take This Off
-OK
Wait
It Is Embarrassed
Such A Embarrassing Posture
I Can See Clearly
-Look
-Don't Be Like This
Don't Look Like This
I Have Taken A Closer Look
Look
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
-Do You Want To See My Face?
-Yes
-Then Hold Back
-Okay
Oh Yeah
Yes, Hold It
-It's Oh Yeah
-Look
Yes
-Hold Back
-Okay
-That
-What's Wrong
Can I Cum A Little Bit?
Not Yet
What Is A Little Bit
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
-Look
-Wait
No Way
-Okay
-So
-Do You Want To See My Face?
-Yes
Yes
-Have You Hold It Back?
-Yes
-Next, Get Me High Too
-Okay
Is That So
-Go On
-Really?
-Take A Closer Look
-Okay
Come On
Can't You See It Again?
Oh Yeah
Come On
Go On
So Soft
If I Get You High
Will You Still Reward Me?
I Have To Get Me High Too
Go On
Come On
Oh Yeah
I Am Coming
Okay
Feeling Good, Right?
Go On
How's It?
Oh Yeah
So Wet
How About Here
Yes, That Is Great
-Feeling Good, Right?
-Lie Down
Can You Give It To Me A Reward
Be Quiet
I Love It
-Do You Like My Feet
-Yes
Oh Yeah
Yes
Really?
Go On
Look
Yes
What Should I Do?
No, My Nipples Are So Sensitive
Yes
This Is So Good
Hold It, There Are More Good Things Waiting For You
Good Thing?
What Is It
Let's Enjoy Ourselves
Okay
-Do You Wanna Do It?
-Yes
Do Something High
Can I?
Open Your Mouth
-Is It Delicious?
-Yes
Yes
-Feeling Good, Right?
-Yes
Let Me See How You Feel Good
Yes
Look
Wait
It's So Intense
-Can I Cum?
-I'm Coming
Okay
Yes
-Pet Me
-OK
Oh Yeah
Wait, This Is So Intense
I'm Coming
Oh Yeah
-That's Awesome
-I Can't Hold It Anymore
Hold Back
-Okay
-Hold Back
Yes, It Is So Good
I'm Fucking Coming
Oh Yeah
I'm Coming
-Fuck Me
-Okay
Is That So
Oh Yeah
-Look
-You Are So Horny
That's Awesome. Go On
So Hot
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Oh Yeah
Fuck Yeah
That's Awesome. Go On
Go On
I'm Coming
Harder
Fuck Me Harder
Yes
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Not Yet
-Hold Back
-Okay
Oh Yeah
I'm Coming
-Fuck Me Harder
-Okay
Oh Yeah
Yes
Come On, Go On
Oh Yeah
I'm Coming
Why Did You Stopped
I'm Fucking Coming
I'm Coming
Go On And Fuck Me Harder
No, I'm Coming
I'm Coming
Oh Yeah
Go On
I'm Coming
-Come Here
-Okay
Oh Yeah
-Come On
-Yes
Hold Back
-Can You Hold It Back?
-Do You Wanna Me Go On?
I Can't Hold My Nipples
Hold Back
Go On
I'm Coming
Can I Cum
-No, Lie Down
-OK
I'm Coming
Go On
-Do You Want To Cum?
-Yes
Really?
Yes
Can't You Hold Back Anymore?
Oh Yeah
Yes
Fuck Yeah
Oh Yeah
I'm Coming
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
-Can I Cum Now?
-Okay
Yes
I'm Fucking Coming
Yes, Give It To Me Your Cum
Oh Yeah
-Little Pig
-Humph
-Thanks
You Are Very Serious
-Me?
-Yes
I Have Confirmed
Have You Confirmed The Photo?
Have You Taken A Good Shot?
No
This Can Be Adjusted
-Did You Think By Yourself?
-Yes
Thank You
-I'm Sorry, Thanks
-Okay
-Do You Wanna Go On
I Had Been Thought About Debut
-It Was The First One At That Time
-Yes
Why Did You Decide To Shoot The Second Work
What I Just Planned To
Shoot One Work
But I Heard That I Received Many
Unexpected Responses
They Wanted Me To Play In The Second Work
I Worked Very Hard As A Limiter
Very Hesitant
I Was Wondering What I Was Thinking About
I Chose This Career Because I Wanted To Be Famous
In Order To Achieve This
I Want To Go On
Then I Took The Second Work
And 2, 3
Is There No Difference?
Yes
-Is It Continuous?
-It Seems To Be
Is There Any Different
Not Like This Before
But That Was From The Fourth Time
-Do You Want To Work Hard As An Porn Movie Actress?
-Yes
It's Different From The First Year So How About The Second Work
The First Work Really
Was Different
I Just Wanted Get Results
Almost Like This
I Hoped Everyone Can See
I Was Looking Forward To It Before
I Told The Porn Movie Producer
I Want To Work Hard
Yes
Then I Think
-Your Body Should Change
-Yes
For Example
From Now
The Person In Charge Is Gone
Do You Remember
Yes
-Indeed
-Just Been Mentioned Suddenly
But The First And Second Parts Are Completely Different
But There Is No Sense Of Contradiction
-I Went To S1 Before
-You Had Changed?
Have You Ever Felt Reluctant In S1?
-Why
-Because You Are Here
I Have Taken Photos Before
But It Can't Be The Same As Before
Very Subtle
I Started To Shoot Serious
In S1
I Just Learned This
I Am Really Happy In S1
Haven't You Thought About Such A Company Like S1?
Yes
I Have A Lot Of Works In S1
Don't You Think You Can't Do It
But I Also Took Out A Few
So For This
On The Contrary, ! Feel Calm
When I Came To S1, I. . . How To Say
Feel Better
And For This Producer
That Was The First Time I Met An Idol To Shot A Porn Movie
Really? I Don't Learn By Myself
-There Are A Few Before.
-Okay
-You Are The Most Shining Star
-I Think So Too
-Really?
-Yes
I Am More Sunny
So I Can Accept How Others See Me
So How To Say
I'm Too Positive
I Just Want To Convey Happiness To Everyone
So I Am Considered Like This
-You Are Always Very Energetic
-Yes
-You can Eat A Lot
-Eat A Lot And Sleep Well
-I See
-Yes
Then So
-There Was A Selection Before
-Yes
Do You Have Any Thoughts On This Award?
How Is It
I Was Looking Forward To
Everyone Said So
So I'm Very Stressed
I Did Not Like This Before
When I Was An Idol
I Did Nothing Great
I've Never Thought That I Did Not Want To Lose
They Always Chose Me And I Never Ask Anyone Else
They Said I Was Selected First
I Should Compete With Others
That Was The First Time
Did You Reject?
I Have Thought About Not Be Be Actress Anymore
I Thought About That
I Had Been Told That My Biggest Competitor Was
Aimi
I Was Very Nervous
We Almost Started Our Career At The Same Time
She Was My Competitor
How Was It Then
Was There An Interview At That Time?
I Didn't Go With Her
You Did
I Thought I Talked About It
She Was Very Gentle And Nice
Although I Wanted To Win
But It Didn't Show My Bad Side
She Will Be Very Happy To Hear That
-She Is Very Gentle
-She Is Very Nice
Then The Senior Actress At That Time
I Cried Because I Was Nervous
At That Time
She Said The Rookie Award Was Very Important
And I Would Be Very Happy If I Won
She Said She Didn't Have It, So She Hoped Me To Win
Very Touched
-Did Girls Even Say That
-Yes, I Was Crying
Very Surprised
-Next
-Okay
I Just Said
After The Event
-Also At That Time
-Yes
A Lot Of Things Have Happened
When I Debuted
There Were Debut Scenes
Was There That Surprised?
-Is It So Long?
-Yes
-It's Been So Long
-And I See
-This Is It
-You Have Changed A Lot
-Yes
There Was A Change
Yes, I Didn't Get It
Rookie Award
I Didn't Get It
Work Award
-Really?
-Yes
:There's-Something Like This When You Move
We Just Talked About It
Muscat
-Muscat
-Yes
I Wanted To Join
When I Started My Porn Movie Career
At That Time Muscat Had Already Formed
I Really Wanted To Go
I Would Be Very Happy After Going
This Was Also An Idol
Did You I Want More To Be An Idol?
Yes
There Are Also Singing And Dancing Places In Porn Movie
I Also Used To Do That
So I Want To Participate
But It Was Completely Different From What I Thought
What Do You Mean
Yes, They Are All Big Idols
With The Way I Think
That Kind Of Cute Looking Is Good
But Is Also A Good Experience
-But It's Interesting
-Yes, It's Interesting.
I Got Used To
How Was It In The Beginning
I Was Asked To Wear Stockings In The First Work
I Felt That I Was Not An Ordinary Idol
-Your Experiences Was Very Rich
-Yes, After I Came
I Can't Say No
All Was Passive
Was In Muscat Or Porn Movie Hard
-Now?
-Yes
-Muscat And Porn Movie
Both
About Porn Movie
The Photography Time And Physical Strength Are Exhausted
It Is Very Hard
Everyone Thinks So
How To Say
It's A Good Scene
But Ebisu Muscat
Really Feel Like A Dog
Of Course No Broker
No Makeup Artist
And Then Be Lubricated
Wet The Body
Lubricant All Over My Body
It Was More Difficult In Muscat
I See
If We Do
The President Will Scold Us
-There Was No Other Way
-Yes, I Will Be Forgiven In Muscat
So Did You Get Used To A Rookie
Yes
So What Was The Situation In The Second Year
There Was Progress At That Time
And When I Joined Into The Muscat
There Were A Lot Of New Jobs
I Was Busy Everyday
No Time To Sleep
I Like Sleeping
I Was Sleeping Almost Every Day
How Long Was The Rest Day
Honestly, One Month
-How Many Times?
-2 Times
I Don't Know If There Is Any
I Can Not Remember
It Was Not Easy
But
That Was
No Pressure
-We Should Talk More
-Yes
Okay
-Let's Change The Place
-Okay, It's So Cold
Sorry
What Do You Want
I Want To Get High
Where Do You Want To Be Touched
Yes
-My Boobs
-Really?
Is This Enough?
Keep Petting Me
Go On?
Kneel
Is It Itchy?
I Will Stop
No
-Do You Want To Be Sucked?
-Yes
How
Caress Me More
Move Your Tongue
Stick Out Your Tongue
-Feeling Good, Right?
-Yes
Relax
Keep Getting Wet
Go On
Your Nipples Are Getting Hard
Yes
Lift Your Legs Up
Then
Feeling Good, Right?
Reach Out Your Hands
Come Here
I Will Suck You
What Do You Do You Wanna Do It Next?
Tell Me
I Want To Get High
Really?
Gently
Or Intense
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Coming
You Can't Come Immediately Like This
-Do You Want To Come?
-Yes
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Coming
Tell Me If You Want To Get High
Please Go On
Okay
I Want To Come
I'm Coming
Do You Want To Come
Raise Up Your Ass
Open It By Yourself
Look At Here
It Is So Wet
So Wet
-Do You Want To Come?
-Yes
Feeling Good, Right?
Yes, I Wanna More
Really?How About This?
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
-I'm Coming
-Really?
-I'm Coming.
-Okay, You Don't Need To Hold It
I'm Coming
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
No, I'm Coming Again
-I'm Coming.
-You Want This, Right?
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Open It More
Oh Yeah
Raise Up Your Ass
Come Here
Relax
Open It Here
Grab Here
Do You Want It?
Yes
I Want More
No, I'm Coming
You Are Really Sensitive
I Will Come Soon
Very Good, Do You Want To Come Inside Too?
-Yes
-Do You Want
Suck Me
Open Your Legs
Beg Me
I Want This
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Yes, That Is Great
I'm Coming
I Have Been Coming
Do You Want To Get High Again?
Yes
I'm Coming
Very Good, You Don't Need To Hold It
Support our new sites:
www.pornDQ.com | www.JAVMARIO.com
Is Inside Your Pussy Feeling Cool?
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
That Is Great
Yes
I'm Coming
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
No, I'm Coming
I'm Coming
Fuck Yeah
Pet Your Pussy
Look At Here
-Do You Want To Suck?
-Yes
I Do
Suck My Whole Body
Yes
You Are Sweating A Lot
Does It Smell
Yes
You Are So Horny
-Do You Want To Suck It?
-Yes
Can You Start Sucking From The Thigh?
Yes
-Do You Want To Be Sucked?
-Yes
Stick Out Your Tongue
Yes
Let Me Listen To Your Moan
Nice
This Is So Cool
Do You Feel Uncomfortable?
Can You Go On?
Suck It By Yourself
Oh Yeah
Masturbate
How's It?Tell Me
-My Pussy Is So Wet
-Really?
Where Do You Want What?Tell Me
My Pussy
Want A Cock
Wet Pussy
Open It And Let Me See
-Can I Fuck You Now?
-Yes
Beg Me
Fuck Me, Please
-Yes
-Feeling Good, Right?
-I'm Coming
-Really?
Am I Fucking You Hard?
Yes
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Coming
Stick Out Your Tongue
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
No, That Is Too Hard
I'm Coming
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Oh Yeah
I'm Coming
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Your Pussy Is So Wet
Yes
I'm Coming
Raise Up Your Ass
Oh Yeah
Fuck Me. Oh Yeah
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Fuck Yeah
I'm Coming
No, I'm Coming
I Am Sorry
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
How About Harder?
No Way
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
No, I'm Coming
I'm Coming
No, I Am Going To Get Crazy
No, I'm Coming
I'm Coming
Fuck Yeah
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Coming
Stick Out Your Tongue
Where Do You Want Me To Cum
Cum In My Mouth
No, I'm Coming
Stick Out Your Tongue
I'm Fucking Coming
-Are You Satisfied?
-Yes
This Is So Fucking Good
I Chose This Stage For This Time
It's Next To The Theater Where Your Debut Was
Next Door?
Isn't It?
-Is This The First One Next Door ?-Yes
-Is It Really Next Door?
-Yes, Next Door
That Was Your First Work
-I See
-The Second Floor
<
Yes
I Used To Come Here Often
When I Was Debuting
-Is It Beautiful And Use It Often?
-It's True
-Isn't It Beautiful?
-But This Place
It Feels Like A Debut
-Only Recently Debuted
-Didn't You Come Recently?
Not Really
Plot, Swimming Pool Or Something
It Has Been Increased Recently
Yes
Are You Good At Plot
No, I Hate That
I Told You I Have No Acting Skills
I Don't Know Why You Want Me To Be Like This
I Do Not Know Why
I Really Have Nothing To Hide
I Don't Want To Have Acting Skills
-Really
-But Your Skill Is So Good
Not At All
How To Say
I Don't Know What Is Necessary
Very Strange
I Was Often Photographed
We Won't End These
We Won't Stop
-But The Porn Movie Is Not Edited, Right?
-Yes
I Don't Know When The Plot Is Popular
Yes, So I Hate That
-Yes
But Someone Just Care The Acting Skill
But Can You Not Just Watch Acting Skill When I Make An Porn Movie
-I'm Sorry.
-Yes
Then
-Let's Go Back
-OK
The Topic Of The Third Year
-The Third Year
-Okay
Do You Remember What You Did
No
When I Debut In The First Year Or The Second Year
I Am Not Very Clear
I Didn't Know Much At First
Also The Second Year, And Started From The Third Year
And Days Too
I Feel I Was Repeating Every Day
Wake Up In The Morning Or Sleep At Night
From The Third Year
I Can't Remember
It Was Over When I Found Out
Did It End Early?
Yes, I Can't Remember
Actually, ! Do
At The End Of The Year, There Is An Award For The Best Actress
-Was That The Third Year?
-Yes
-Is It The End Of The Year?
Indeed, If So
Maybe
I See, Sorry
Yes
It Is Hard To Say
Didn't You Get The Best Prize?
The Top Actress I Told
-Are You Conscious?
-Not At All
-Really?
-Tell The Truth
It Was Very Different
To Be Honest, This Kind Of
Among So Many Great Actresses
I Didn't Expect To Get The First
I Was Scared
Can You Be Specifically?
But
When I Got This
I Want To Thank My Fans
I Held A Free Photo Session
At 6 Places In The Country
Yes
Meet The Fans Directly Like This
Met Many People Who Supported Me
I Was Very Happy
They Were Very Gentle
Many People Came To Play
I Was Scared
They Even Came To See Me Like This
You Were Number One In Japan At That Time
But That Was
A Good Experience
So As Just Said
Was That Very Different
How To Say That?It Has The
First Year, And The First Three Years
That Difference
-Yeah
-The Photography Or Something
Don't Like Too Horny
Because I Took The Winning Prize
And There Are A Lot Of Job Opportunities For Me
I May Have Taken
There Were A Lot Of New Jobs Came To Me
I Don't Know How To Say
I Can't Remember The Days
At That Time
I Worked Hard
You Were Better
Than Now
There Were Many Projects
On 2017, Right?
CO-Acting, Right?
Co-Act
Isn't It
Not In A Hurry
Yes
-My Own Various Works
-Yes
Yes, The First Work
Super Bukkake
. Was That In The Third Year?
-Yes
I Thought It Was Earlier
Then 31 Packages
Was That Also In The Third Year?
-4 Hours A Day
-I Worked Very Hard At That Time
Yes, It Will Be More Intense Afterward
92 Orgasms
-Super High Frequency
-It Seems To Be Here
Very Erotic
Then Be Fucked Immediately In The Four Work
In My Opinion, That Was
Very Early
All Were Recently
You Shot A tot Of Movie, And Me Too
The Users Are Different
-Do You Wanna Thank Your Fans?
-Yes
You Took A Very Good Work
Okay
Then
Was There Anything Impressive
The Bukkake Was Not Easy
How About The Works
What Was It Then
A Lot Of Bukkake
I Had To Go Back And Makeup Again Every Time
I Was Told That My Eyes Were Congested
My Eyes Had Been Cum
Eyes Were Bloodshot
Then The Next Day
My Skin Was Rough
Really?
Because Of Semen
That Was It After Taking A Shower
I See
There Were A Lot
Is That So?So Much? That's Great
It Was Not Just Me
Yes
But It Feels Different From Normal
Very Exciting
So
Was That In Your 3 Years?
No
But 31 Was Quite Commemorative
Did You See It
Yes
You Worked Hard
31 Packages
It Has Changed
Yes
Okay
You Are Really Not Easy
Especially
Isn't This Cos Photography 31
-There Must Be More
-No
Not Porn Movies
You Have A Lot Of Photography
Then, About The Type
I Want To Ask You Something
Do You Like Sex
It's Weird If I Say I Don't Like It
Okay, Another Question
What Kind Of Sex Do You Like?
There Are Also Many Plans For This
Normal Sex
I Like It Better
I Don't Need To Care About The Camera
That Is Better
Do You Like That?
Yes
Are There Any Types That You Are Not Good At?
Rated
Really Oh Yeah
But That Is Very Popular
But Your Rated Works
Are So Few, But It's Pretty Good
Really?But It Was Exciting At That Time
Not Lately
I See
Are You Not Good At Being Caressed?
Yes, The Unknown Is Terrible
So Are You A Sadism Or A Masochism
S At The Beginning
And M After?
If You Have To Count, That Is M
I Am S
It's Better To Be Caressed
But Now, I Like To Caress Men
Okay
Just Always
-And Then Is The Fourth Year
-Okay
Okay
-Please Excuse Me
-Okay
Look At Here
Kiss Me
You Are So Horny
Yes, That Is Great
Support our new sites:
www.pornDQ.com | www.JAVMARIO.com
Yes
-Feeling Good, Right?
-Yes
Come Here
Nice
Oh Yeah
Feeling Good, Right?
-It's Oh Yeah, Yes
-Go On?
Yeah
Yes
Oh Yeah
Come Here
How About Here
How Is That?
Oh Yeah
I'm Coming
Yes
Here
Suck Me
I'm Coming
Are You Coming?
Look At Here, Suck It For Me
Yes
Keep Sucking My Cock
Let's Suck Together
Oh Yeah
Fuck Yeah
Turn Around
Nice
Come Here
Fuck Yeah
Yes
Oh Yeah
-Do You Want My Cock?
-Yes
Give It To Me
Do It Yourself
Oh Yeah
So Big Of Your Cock
Yes
Oh Yeah
No, I'm Coming
I'm Coming
Oh Yeah
Yes
I'm Coming
Get Up
Yes
This Is So Cool
Oh Yeah
I'm Coming
Turn Over
Suck Me
Come On, Suck Me
Fuck Yeah
Go On
I Want More
No, I'm Coming
I'm Coming
Oh Yeah
Yes
It's Awesome
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Coming
Feeling Good, Right?
Yes
I'm Coming
Pet His Cock
Oh Yeah
I Want This
Yes
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Yes, That Is Great
I'm Coming
Oh Yeah
Yes
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Coming
Raise Up Your Ass With Your Hands
Yes, Raise Up Your Ass
Here
This Is So Cool
I'm Coming
Oh Yeah
No, I'm Coming
Yes
This Is So Cool
Get Up
Oh Yeah
Here
I'm Coming
Oh Yeah
-Feeling Good, Right?
-Yes
How About This?
This Is So Fucking Good
Fuck Yeah
Oh Yeah
I'm Coming
I'm Coming.
-Is It Cool?
Suck My Cock
I'm Coming
Yes
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
-I'm Coming
-Let Me See You Come
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Oh Yeah
Yes
No, I'm Coming
Look At Here
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Fucking Coming
Yes, Give It To Me Your Cum
-Is It Okay
-Yes, Give It To Me Your Cum
-I'm Fucking Coming It
-Give It To Me That Cum
I'm Fucking Coming
Oh Yeah
Yes
Yes, That Is Great
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Coming
-Feeling Good, Right?
-Yes
Yes
-I'm Coming
-It's I'm Fucking Coming
-Can I Cum On Your Face?
-Yes, Give It To Me That Cum
I'm Fucking Coming
-Let's Go Back At 2018
-Okay
4 Years In This Industry
4 Years
You Are Still The Top One
-Yes
-Your Evaluation Is Very Good
Yes
But You Didn't Realize It
I Won't Say It Myself
Don't You Think You Can Be Better?
I Will Think So If I Look At The Data
But About The Top One
I Don't Know
-But The Younger Generation Has Increased
-Yes
Anyway
I Also Often Ask Others
What Kind Of Person Do They Want To Become
Many Peoples Said They Wanted To Be Like You
-A Lot?
-A Lot
I Am So Happy
I Didn't Ask Directly
I Rarely See Other Actresses
I Don't Have That Conscious
Don't You Have Any Juniors In The Same Office?
-Yes
-Moeko Miko
Yes
Are You Together?
Are You Cold?
No, It Feels Okay
Pretty Good
It Doesn't Feel Like A Senior
I Don't Care Too Much
-May I Ask?
-Okay
Would You Hate It If You Were Called Intimate?
I Have Never Been Called Like That
It's Okay If Someone Get Along With Me
You Are Broad-Minded
I Don't Think Too Much
Will You Be Angry?
Yes
Like What?
Uhh, If I Did Something Wrong At Work?
I Will Be Scold By The Office President
Office President?
Yes
What Exactly?
The Agent Won't Be Angry
Will You Be Scolded For Not Doing Your Job Well?
-Yes
-I See
But In This Case
There Are Also Many Changes
-Co-Acting
-Here
-Is That A Lot?
-No
Only 3 Times
In This Case
The VR Co-Starring With Hashimoto Arina
And Co-Acting With Takahashi
-You Really Got Something
-I Still Remember
-Wouldn't You Watch It When You Play With Other Actresses?
-Yes
What Do You Think
That's Awesome
The Girl You Know Was Having Sex
That Was Weird
I Would Get Used To It After Having Sex On The First Day
Yes
It Was Shocking At First
Which On Was In The Beginning
Should Be S1
-I See. Were There 7 People?
-Yes
No
7 People
What Kinds Of ?
That?
Yes, That Summer Special Work
I Went To Saitama
Yes
Was There Anyone Who Impressed You At That Time?
Some Rookies
But I Have Almost Seen Them All
But We Almost Interacted Together
That Was Arely
What Exactly?
There Won't Be Anyone You Don't Know
I Knew Everyone, So I Didn't Worry
Aren't You Embarrassing?
Everyone Has Promiscuity
That Was Interesting
It Was Fun
I Thought I Was Hated
Absolutely Not
I Found Someone Was In Front Of My Ass
That Was Very Shocking
There Were 2 People Together Before
Very Funny
-Really?
-Because Of Her Partner Actor
Was Very Aggressive
It Was Very Interesting
-You Laughed
-A Lot Of Things Happened
I Didn't Realize It Too Much
Didn't My Clip End Right Away?
I Felt Weird Afterward
Was He Shot Midway?
-Really?
-Yes
I See
I Did Not Know
I Just Felt Weird
I Didn't Know What Happened
That Was The Development, It's Very Interesting
-Do You Remember It
-Yes
-She Was Troubled, Right?
But You Helped Her
-Did I?
-Yeah, And You Said Come On
Because It Was Really Interesting
And Easier
But It Was Really Good
Really?
Now My Goal Is Documentary
So, You Are Used To It For The Fourth Year.
But Still Not Good At Rated Type, Right?
Yes
Won't You Cry
-Acting Skill?
-Do You Find It More Difficult?
I Have Cried
That Was
I Exchanged With Takahashi
We Exchange Our Works
Producer Exchange?
Yes, When Shoot At MOODYZ
The Director I Met For The First Time
That Was Very Long
Every Link
At The Beginning, ! Worked Hard
The Link Was Very Long
The Actor Was Not Doing Well
I Helped Him In The Beginning
Then Let Him Get Hard-On And Fuck Me
And We Did That 3 Times
Actually It Was Over 12 O'clock
Then I Felt That I Would That That For The Rest Of My Life
I Can't See The End
Then I Said I Wanted To Go To The Toilet
Then I Cried When I Went Back
Why Did I
Helped So Many Times
But Resurrected Again
And Go On Like This
I Thought About That
Then Cried For The First Time
Were 'You Embarrassing When The Actor Could Not Get Hard-On?
No, But That
I Had Hold A Lot Of Sadness That Day
I Thought He Would Cum, And It Would Be Over When He Cum.
I Thought It Was Over
But After 40 Minutes
I Felt That It Would Not Be End
Then I Asked The Director
He Said He Was Like That Every Time
I Wondered Why Kept Letting Him Come
It Was Weird
-Then, The People You Saw Were Very Delicate, Right?
-Yes
Then There Were Changes
Do You Know
-No
-No?
And There Was A Girl Who Had Co-Acting With Me
-Acting Together, Actress?
-I Don't Know
She Was Member Of The Former Idol Team
-Okay
-Can I Say I Didn't Do It For You
-Her?
-Yes
-Variety Show?
I Met The Member For The First Time
-Yes
-It Should Be
That Is Good
So, About This
She Did Not Come To Us
We Are Different
That's It
Wasn't It Embarrassing To Meet After A Long Time?
No, But She
Galled Me By My Previous Name
She Was My Junior
She Said She Liked Me Very Much And Supported Me
I'll Meet In Variety Shows Later
She Will Also Reply Me On INS Now
"
-But It Was All Scripts
-Yes
How Did You Feel When You Know Her Name
She Would Say Come On
It's Been A Long Time
When I Was An Idol
It's Not The Kind That We Had A Very Good Relationship
I Feel The Same As Before
We Would Chat When You Meet
Also At That Time
Although We Haven't Played Together
But That Was No Difference
Yes
Can I Ask A Final Question
In Your 4 Years
Do You Feel That You Have Become A Real Porn Movie Actress
-Really?
-Yes
Maybe Earlier
Before
Porn Movie Career
Was There Any Difference From You Think?
I Had That Feeling In The First Year
About The Initial Impression
I Didn't Feel Bad At First
Because There Is Such A Career
Everyone Will Watch Porn Movie
I Didn't Expect Myself To Be Like This
It Is A Very Incredible World
After I Joined, Unexpectedly
I Became A
Porn Movie Actress, ! Quite Enjoyed
One
Thank You For Your Talking
-Anyway, This Is The Fourth Year
-Okay
Thank You
(You Are Very Beautiful Recently) (Was There Anything You Did?)
With My Body?
Compared To Debut
I Was Just Losing Weight
And Then Took The Photography
Nothing Else
I Started Eating Recently
I Will Eat Italian Noodles
And I Will Make It At Home
(Which Part Of Your Body Do You Like Most?
Waist
That Is
Yesterday, ! Just Measured My Waist
Is 58cm
And So
I Think This Is A Charm
(That's Good)
I Didn't Expect, And I Am Very Happy
(I Want To Take A Closer Look At Your Body) (Can You Take It Off?)
In Here?
I Have Done This In My Debut
How Should I Start
(It Is Up To You)
Really?
Support our new sites:
www.pornDQ.com | www.JAVMARIO.com
Neck (Can I See Your Neck)
Is It Better To Take This Off? (Yes)
Okay (That Is Great)
It Is Embarrassed
(Nice Body)
It's Not Easy To Get Some Weight Here
But Not Elsewhere
My Belly Won't Have Any Excrescence
(That Is Good)
What Are You Doing?
Make Me Feel Embarrassed
(Can I See Your Ass?)
(Your Ass Is Also Very Good)
Really?
I Have Exercised My Ass
(Can You Take That Off?)
Is This An Interview
This Is Not Like A Sex
It Is Embarrassed To Be Photographed Like This
(That's Good)
What
(Is It Okay To Put Your Hands Down)
(I Want To Say That Your Boobs Are So Beautiful)
Really?
(Have You Been Said Like This?)
I Am Happy To Hear That
(Nice Nipples)
Nipple?
(Can You Take Off Your Panties?)
Panties?
All Right
It Is Embarrassed
(Your Body Is Really Good)
(Can You Approach The Camera?)
Come Close?
Okay
(Are You Embarrassing?)
Yes
(I'm Going To Pet Your Horny Body)
Okay
It Is Itchy
Your Hands Are So Cold
So Soft
Do You Want To Pet Like This?
How Can I Get You High?
It Is Embarrassed, The Same As When I Debuted
How About This?
I Like Gently
So Intense
Your Nipples Are Getting Hard
Feeling Good, Right?
I Want To Laugh
It's So Long, This Caressing
They Are Shaking So Badly
This Is So Cold
My Boobs Are Real Ones
-I Don't Know
-Why
So Soft
I Can't Hold It
Open Your Legs
I Wanna See Your Ass
Raise Up Your Ass
Are You Going To Pet It?
Raise Up Your Ass And Relax
Your Butthole
Relax
Wait
What
Why
This Is Not Oil
Relax
My Fingers Are In
Let Me See Here
-Feeling Good, Right?
-Yes
No, I'm Coming
Great
I Want To Suck It
Can You Sit On Me?
Sit On?
Nice
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I Want To Be Sucked Too
Okay
What's Coming
Do You Want This
Oh Yeah
So Hard Of Your Cock
Yes, So Big
Yes
-Can I Suck It?
-Of Course
I Wanna Fuck You
Can I
Okay
Yes
-Oh Yeah
-Yes
Look At Here
Yes
No, I'm Coming
Oh Yeah
Yes
So Tight Of Your Pussy
No, I'm Coming
Can I Fuck You From Behind
This Is So Good
Please Lie Down. Yes
I'm Coming
No, I'm Coming
Come Here
Relax
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Coming
Hands Up
Can You Sit On Me
I'm Coming
No, I'm Coming
Lie Down
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Fucking Coming
It Is Weird
No One Is Here
Is It Here?
This
Welcome
Why
I Really Want To See You
Long Time No See
Long Time No See. I Haven't Seen You At The Scene.
-On The Street
-Yes, Shibuya
There Are Activities On The Street
Didn't We See Each Other After That?
Yes
What About Make Love
-Make Love?
-Make Love Is. .
-The Hard Kind
-Hard?
Yes
Before This
It Might Be The Kind Of Coffee Shop
-That's Early
-How Early
3 Years Ago
-Right?
-So
Actually We Never Did It Again
Can We Do That Today?
Yeah, Look At Here
Bed
And Also
This DVD
-Do You Remember?
-My First Work Of S1?
Yes
Why Did You Put It In Here
Did You Read It
Yes And Get Excited
And Then I Wanna Fuck You
-Will You Watch Your Own Work?
-No
I Have Seen Before
Will You Watch Your Own Work?
-No
-Why
-But
-You Have Played A Lot, Right?
Yes
I Think How To Edit It When I Watched It
But I Rarely Watch
-Will You Watch Porn Movie?
-Yes
I Have Watched A Lot. When I Watched
I Will Contact The Director If I Think That Girl |s Cute
Say You Want To See Her?
-Yes
-What Else
-I Will Ask How.
-Really?
Yes
Is This Often?
Very Few, Everyone Is Lively
-Is Anything Okay?
-Yes, Because Of The Actor
Everyone Has Advantages
We Will Help You Find Out
-Great
-Then
Before Watching This
Let Me Think About It
-Tell The Truth
-Okay
Anyway, There Are Just Two Of Us
It's Been 5 Years, Right?
Yes, Almost 6 Years
-6th Anniversary Soon.
-I See
You Are Very Sophisticated
I Don't Like This
Really?So What Do You Like?
-Rookie?
-Yes
They Keep Yourself As 18 Years Old
Okay
Are There Any Competitors For You?
It's Been A Long Time
There Was At The Beginning
Should It Be A Competitor?
But We Often Worked Together
That Actress
-Really?
-Yes
And GaoXi
We Will Work Together
But Not A Competitor
We Had Never Acted Together
-Really?
-We Completely Not See Each Other
-Your Work Has Changed
-Yes
Are There Any Actresses That Worth You To Pay Attention Now?
Do You Seldom Watch?
Yes, But I'll Watch It On The Social Network
-Where?Are There Any Different Manufacturers?
-Yes
-I Want To Know
-What
Cute Girls
-Cute Girls
-Then
I Haven't Seen
Mihara
-Xiaoxi?
-Yes
-Is Xi As Hope?
I Saw It On Social Software And I Think She Is So Cute
-She Is Debut
-Really?
-Yes
-She Is Cute
-Look At This
-What
There Are A Lot Of Actresses I've Seen, I Can Write
-I Want To See
-Really?
Was I In That?
Yes
I Want To See Mine
Wait A Minute. It Was Taken In My Phone.
You Laughed
Previous Director
Will Take Off This
You Will Be Asked About What Is It Like
-Really?
-Yes
So Let Me Show It To You First
Oh Yeah
Yes
That's It
That Is So Bright
You Are Pretty
Fatty
-Do You Wanna See?
-It Is Terrible
Labia Majora
-I'm Going To Say
-Okay
Fleshy Labia Majora
Labia Minora Is Very Horny
-This Is Very Detailed
-The Asshole Is Very Beautiful
The Most Beautiful I Have Ever Seen
It Feels Delicious And The Personality Is Cute
Uhh
Kissing Is Good
Lips Are Too Soft
That's It. How About This?
-Do You Like It?
-This Was The First Time, Right?
Yes
Do You Like It
All Has Been Written Down
Oh Yeah
These Contents
And That Is
Do You Usually Rest
Sometimes
How Many Times A Month
Not Too Much
Maybe Once A Week
You Are Busy
What Else Do You Do Except This?
And Ebisu Muscat Rated
And
Lingerie Model
Prostitution Shops Advertisement
-I See
-Yes
Then These 5 Years
Are There Any Thoughts?
Any Thoughts?! Never Thought Of Leaving
But Almost None
Although There Are Things I Don't Like
How To Overcome
I Will Forget When I Sleep
This Is Very Important
Will You Consider That?
No
-Really?
-Yes
I Like Sleeping
I Don't Have Time To Sleep If There Was Something I Worry About
People Who Look At This Will Be Surprised, Right?
-Really?
-This Kind Of Thing
I Didn't Expect It To Be Forever
So Go To Bed Early At Night
-Yes, Before 10 O'clock At Night
-Do You Think Something Annoying?
-Yes
-Negative Emotions
Yes
Do You Want To Get Married
I Have Often Been Asked This
No, I Don't Want To
Marriage Is Hell
Everyone Who Watches This Is Married
This Can't Be Posted, Right?
This Is Normal
Are You Feeling Cool?
Has This Been Released?
-Yes
-80%
What's Going On
There Is A Sound, It's Too Low To Make Sense
Really?
(Marriage Topic Is Too Long, Cut It)
But It's Different From Men
Men Are Very Enthusiastic At First
Very Subtle
And Because They Like Me
Then The Man Is Busy With Work
-The Wife Will Feel Tired Of It.
-No
Women Like The Process Of Socializing
Through Association
-That's It
-That's Very Troublesome
Right?
He Would Pick Me Up Before, But Not Now
But There Will Be A Better Man
That Kind Of Person
-There Are Also Things I Haven't Thought Of
-Yes
-Then There Are Similarities
-Indeed
-Yes
-Is He Worthy Of Respect
-Yes, But He Will Cheat
-There Are People Who Have Not Cheated
-No, Absolutely No
-Who Do You Think?
-Yes
Really
-Man
-What's Up
Will Cheat
There Will Be Men Who Will Not Cheat
Porn Movie Actor Will Not
For Example, Do You Have
-Do You?
-Yes
Who
-Tell Me, I Won't Tell Others
-Someone Will Hear
-No
-There Is Really Some
-Normal Ones
I Would Never Tell Others, Because
-You Will Write It On Your Notes, Right?
-Absolutely No
-You Will
-No
No
For Example,
If There Was A Man Who Had Dating With Me
Then Why Did You Break Up
I Was A Little Tired
If You Are Tired, There Is No Way
Tired Of Shifting Is
I Don't Want To Get Married
-I Want To Love More.
-I See
-You Have Been Dating For 3 Years
-Did I Say This
No, Not Tired
So, You Are
Very Old-Fashioned
Right?But There Are Some Men Who I Think It Is Suitable For Marriage
Indeed, Marriage And Dating Are Not The Same Thing
-They Are Different
-Yes
Maybe When Will Come
There Must Be Such A Person
-How Come
-I Believe It
You Will Know That Nature Is Better Than Betrayal
Indeed, I Knew Some Of Them Would Cheat
But I Hope They Will Not To Be Discovered By Me
You Can Cheat, But You Can Not Be Exposed
-This Is Right
-Yes
-We Have Been Talking For 30 Minutes
Yes, We Only Have One Hour
Really?
-Can It Be Extended?
-Only 1 Hour
-Can It Be Extended
-No
Okay
-Okay Then
-Chatting Is So Fun
The Power Has Dropped
That Has Dropped
Which One Is Me
-You Were In
-Which One
It Should Be 2
2?
8 Links
I Tried Too Hard
Is This The Next One?
This
I Was So Young
So Fresh
I Worked So Hard
Wait A Minute, What
What? Say It Again
-I Worked So Hard
-Don't You Work Hard Now
No, Not Like This
I Was Old-Fashion At That Time
I Did Not Know Anything
I Felt That The Industry Had A Bright Future Waiting For Me
Wait, If That So
When You Understand This Now
Did You Get Hurt?And Did You See The Dark Side
No
I Didn't Know At That Time
Indeed
-You Were So Young At That Time
-Yes
-Fresh
-A Rookie
I Didn't Expect That I Would Be So Busy At Work
100% Energetic
-Relax
-Okay
Very Energetic
Yes, Look At This
What Did You Just Said
That Was Too Energetic
Read As Above
-But You Are Okay Now
-Yes
Yes, But I Think You Were Cute
-Yes, Now Is Mature
-More Calm
Yes
Very Meaty
-Meaty?
-Don't You Think?
What About Now?
Not As Fat As This
Uhh
There Were Some Scenes I Like
-Favorite Scene
-I Was In
Yes, Blue Clothes
You Are So Easy To Be Recognized
-This Hairstyle
-No, I Am Embarrassing
Sorry
Stop Talking, It Is Embarrassed
-That's Great
-This Is So Good
-This
-What's Wrong
Can You See It
This Fleshy Armpit
-Has Been Separated
-Why Is This
Also Between The Thighs
Really Pitiful
What Are You Doing
I Know Nothing At All
With This Pose
I Can't Stand It Anymore
Don't Say You Are Pitiful
That's All
Look At This
-This Doesn't Seem To Be Coded
-Yeah
Wait, This Avatar
-Avatar?
-Avatar
Because
It's Weird To See My Own Work
And So Early One
The Recent Ones Are Okay
Really?
Recently
This Dress
I Really Like It
-Do You Like This? Is It Popular?
-Yes
Lie Down
-Really?
-If You Did Not Do This
You Are Very Popular Too
If You Lie Down Like This
I Feel That You Would Say That To Everyone
You Are Special
Really?
-Wait
-Wait, My Pussy Is Exposed
Exposed
My Cunts Are Exposed
The Panties Is Too Small, I Have Seen It All
Yes
Be Careful
It Has Really Been Exposed
Put It On Well
This Panties Is So Small
-It Is Embarrassed
-It's Okay
Aren't You Hairless
No
Really?
But The Hair Has Been Removed. It Should Be
The Hair Has Been Blocked
Sorry, Let Me Cover It
-You Failed
-Really?
That Is Terrible
It's Been A Long Time
Yua's Pussy
Are You Keeping Shooting
-Don't You Like It
-No
-This Is A Private Shot
-Private Shot?
Haven't You Tried This Before?
Yes
But Rarely
Look
Don't Shoot Here. Come On
Don't Suck It
All Right
I Kissed Such A Cute Girl
How To Take This Off
From Here
-Dress?
-Yes
Really Beautiful
I Haven't Seen It Like This
-Don't You Need To Untie It?
-Is That So
-Take It Off
-Now?
The Time Is Running Out
It Is Okay
-The Areola Is Exposed
-Isn't It?
This Size Is Not Suitable
Wait, Let Me Help You
The Way Of Taking Off Is So Strange, Come On
-You Are Really Mess Up
-What's Up
Come On
Is It Okay Now? Take It Off
Nice
It Did Show Up
So Beautiful
-It Was Too Fast
-You Are So Horny
It Was Too Fast
Wait, It Is Embarrassed
So Soft
Put It Down, Okay?
Can You Do This?
Yes
It's A Long Time. How About This?
Isn't This A Private Shot?
Wait
Wait, What?
What?Don't Do This
Wait
-No
-Why Not
Uhh
-So Beautiful
-No
Not Pretty
I Didn't Take A Bath
Wait
Don't You Take A Bath?
My Former Actor
When I Was A Rookie
They Said To Take A Bath
It Turned Out That The Bathroom Was Not Wet
I Thought They Were Inside
They Only Washed The Pussy
That's It
Right?
-Today Is Okay
-Then
If We Take A Bath Later
I'll Suck It For You
So Beautiful
-What Is Beautiful Or Not Clean?
-Nothing Is Dirty
Is That So?
Look At The Camera, Look At Here
-You Like Your Underarms Too Much, Don't You
-Always
Look At The Armpit
Everyone Doesn't Like This, Right?
This Is. .
Ask Your Fans
How About This?
-You Have To Remember To Ask
-Okay
Asshole Is Not Good
Your Hands Are So Wet
Why
It Is So Weird
-Various Kinds Of
-Okay
Media Or Something
I Always Said That You Have The Most Beautiful Asshole
No
So Beautiful
Wait, Come On
Not This
That Is Too Close
Wait
So Wet
Yes
That Is Too Close
It Is Really Beautiful
-I Can See Clearly
-No
I Am Coming
All Right
If There Is No Time
Just Let Me Hurry Up
Is The Strength Appropriate?
You Are Keeping Sucking
It Is Very Delicious
No?
Do You Hate Being Sucked?
-Yua
-What's Wrong
Your Pussy Is So Wet
You Are So Horny
That Is Too Close
Your Love Juice Is Flowing Out
-Lie Down
-Lie Down?
What A Beautiful Ass
I Always Read It In The Magazine
Asshole
-I Saw It
-No
Oh Yeah
Wait
Not Asshole
Can I Suck It?
No Way
-Please
-No
Absolutely Not
No Way
-It's Okay If It's Just A While
-Okay
Really Just A While
-I Am Coming
-No, You Can't Suck
How Is It?Just A While
-I Promised
-Yes
-Not Bad, Right?
-It's Over
-One More Time
-Okay
Just Once?
Come On
So Hard Of Your Cock
Do You Mean. .
Uhh
It Has Skipped
Really?
May Be
Come On
Don't
Maybe It's Weird
This Is Also The Feeling Of Summer
-Why Didn't You Wash It
-Because
20 Years
Will Skip
No
This Response
Stinky Cock
Don't Smell Like This
Because
What A Stinky Cock
It Needs To Be Washed
Then Do You Wanna Me Clean It With My Saliva?
Suck It First
So Cute
Look At Here, You Are So Cute
Nice
Swallow My Love Juice
Come On
Oh Yeah
Your Ass Is So Soft
Here Is
So Hard
This Is Incredible
Come On, Let's Have Sex
Time Is Running Out
Yes, I Really Want To Extend It
Can I Fuck You Without A Condom?
No
I Will Fuck You Like This
No Way
I Told You That At The Beginning
That's It
What
You Asked Me Whether You Can Fuck Me Without A Condom
It Won't Be Shown In The Main Story
-You Won't Tell?
-Yes
Let's Begin
So Soft
So Hard Of Your Cock, Why?
Why
Is That So?
You Are Often Like This
Having Sex Without A Condom Will Be So Good
Yes
Yua's Pussy Is So Good
What Kind Of Looking Is This
You Are So Cute
Oh Yeah
Fuck Yeah
Here
Your Pussy Is So Tight
Fucking You Without A Condom Like This
Your Pussy Will Be So Tight
Then My Semen, That. . .
Will Flow Out
It Will Be Better If You Ovulate
-No
-No?
Yua
Fuck Yeah
Are You Okay?
Do You Feel Uncomfortable?
Oh Yeah
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Next
I Didn't Hear Anything
Maybe That
Fuck Me Harder Like That
Yes
Fuck It If You Want
I Do Not Know
Are You Okay? Rubbing Like This
Rubbing Like This
Yes
No Way
You Are So Horny
Do You Want Me To Cum Quickly?
-No
-Don't Do This
-No, Stop It
-Are You Really Coming?
Stop, Please
-Are You Coming?
-Hold The Back With Your Hands
Why
Can You?
-You Are So Horny
-Why
Can't You Hold Back Anymore?
I Don't Know Your Condition
How Can I Know
-If You Tremble, I Will Know
-Really?
-Then Just Fuck It Like This
-Not All
-So Jealous
-We Are
So Jealous
Let Me Fuck You From Behind
Please
Just Give Me Your Cum
We Have Talked For So Long After We Have Sex
So Beautiful
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Yes
I'm Coming
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
Yes
Feeling Good, Right?
I'm Coming
No, I Can't Hold It Anymore
I'm Fucking Coming
Watch JAV English Subtitles
JAVENGLISH.CC | ~ JAVENGLISH.NET ~ | JAVSUBBED.NET
Goodbye
Thank You, Yua
Come On For Another 100 Years
-Don't Be Like This
-Just Live Well
Everyone, My 6th Anniversary Commemorative Work
Are You Satisfied?
Was There Any Scenes You Like?
Please Tell Me How You Feel
Although It Has Been 6 Years
I Will Continue My Activities In The Future
I Will Still Work Hard On My Porn Movie Career
I Will Work Hard To Improve Myself In The Future
I Need The Hotels Support Me
Please Support Me In The Future
That's All. I'm Mikami Yua
Goodbye
(It's The 6th Anniversary) (Thank You All For Your Support)
(Thank You For Being With Me All The Time, Thank You) (I Will Work Hard In The Future, I Love You)
(Mikami Yua)